- Did you see this viral photo?
- 你看到这张疯传的照片了吗？
Did you see this right here?
你在这里看到这个了吗？
- [Audience] Yes.
- [观众] 是的。
- These kindergartners, they're best friends.
- 这些幼儿园的孩子，他们是最好的朋友。
And they had Twin Day at school.
他们在学校度过了双胞胎日。
So they wanted to dress alike on Twin Day.
所以他们想在双胞胎日穿得一样。
And so here they are.
所以他们就在这里。
Please welcome, Miles and Tanner,
欢迎，迈尔斯和坦纳，
and their moms, (audience cheering)
还有他们的妈妈（观众欢呼）
(audience cheering)
（观众欢呼）
Britney and Lakendra.
布兰妮和拉肯德拉。
Okay, Britney, what's the story behind the photo?
好吧，布兰妮，这张照片背后的故事是什么？
- Well, it was Red Ribbon Week at school
- 嗯，那是学校的红丝带周
and it's Twin Day,
而且今天是双子日，
and so Miles really wanted to dress like Tanner.
所以迈尔斯真的很想穿得像坦纳一样。
And he was adamant that they look identical
他坚称它们看起来一模一样
and that they had the same hair and the same eyes.
他们有相同的头发和相同的眼睛。
Right? (laughs) (audience laughing)
正确的？ （笑）（观众笑）
- He just, that's what he saw?
- 他只是，这就是他所看到的？
- Yes, exactly. - We got the same eyes.
- 是的，完全正确。 - 我们有同样的眼睛。
- Same eyes, same hair.
- 一样的眼睛，一样的头发。
- All right, so what happened the next day at school?
- 好吧，那么第二天在学校发生了什么？
- Well, the night before,
- 嗯，前一天晚上，
you know, I never heard of Tanner or met Tanner.
你知道，我从未听说过坦纳或见过坦纳。
I didn't know him. - Oh, you'd never met him?
我不认识他。 - 哦，你从没见过他？
- No, and so I started stalking
- 不，所以我开始跟踪
everyone in our town to try and find his mother.
我们镇上的每个人都试图找到他的母亲。
So I text the teacher
于是我给老师发短信
and she did give me Tanner's mother's name.
她确实告诉了我坦纳母亲的名字。
just to, you know, common courtesy,
只是为了，你知道，出于礼貌，
like, I'm gonna send some clothes tomorrow
比如，我明天要送一些衣服
(audience laughing)
（观众笑）
for your kid to change into.
让您的孩子变成。
I need you to be on board with me,
我需要你和我一起在船上
you know? - Yeah.
你知道？ - 是的。
- And so he did.
- 他也这么做了。
So we sent in the clothes to school
所以我们把衣服送到学校
and he went and changed as soon as he got there.
他一到那里就去换衣服。
And then the teacher had sent us that picture of the boys,
然后老师给我们发了那张男孩们的照片，
and I was like, "Aw!" (laughs) (audience laughing)
我当时想，“噢！” （笑）（观众笑）
- So you had no idea
- 所以你不知道
who Tanner was? - No.
坦纳是谁？ - 不。
No, not at all. - You just bought the clothes
不，一点也不。 - 你刚买了衣服
'cause your boy came in and said,
因为你的男孩进来说，
"I got the dude at school." - Yes.
“我在学校找到了那个家伙。” - 是的。
- "We got the same eyes." - Yeah.
- “我们有一样的眼睛。” - 是的。
- "Same hair, everything." - Yeah.
- “同样的头发，一切。” - 是的。
- [Steve] Hey, Tanner, Tanner.
- [史蒂夫]嘿，坦纳，坦纳。
Tanner.
皮匠。
- Yes? (audience laughing)
- 是的？ （观众笑）
- Why is Miles your twin?
- 为什么迈尔斯是你的双胞胎？
- Because he wanna be my friend.
- 因为他想成为我的朋友。
- Aw! - Yeah.
- 噢！ - 是的。
And Miles, why did you tell your mom
还有迈尔斯，你为什么告诉你妈妈
that he was your twin?
他是你的双胞胎？
- Yeah. He was my best friend.
- 是的。他是我最好的朋友。
- He's your best friend.
- 他是你最好的朋友。
(audience applauding) That's all that matter.
（观众鼓掌）这就是最重要的。
So y'all twins.
所以你们都是双胞胎。
- And we're both five.
- 我们都是五岁。
- Huh? - We're both five.
- 啊？ - 我们都是五岁。
- Oh, you're both five.
- 哦，你们都五岁了。
Well that hell,
好吧，那个地狱，
that'll do it right there. (audience laughing)
就在那里做。 （观众笑）
- [Britney] Oh my gosh.
- [布兰妮] 天哪。
You did great.
你做得很好。
- Why do you think that many,
- 为什么你认为这么多，
Lakendra and Britney, why do you think
拉肯德拉和布兰妮，你认为为什么
so many people love this story that it went viral?
这么多人喜欢这个故事，以至于它疯传了？
- I think in the media today,
- 我认为在今天的媒体上，
we see a lot of,
我们看到很多，
not the best stories I guess you could say.
我想这不是你能说的最好的故事。
(audience laughing)
（观众笑）
And so- (Miles laughs)
所以——（迈尔斯笑）
(Britney and audience laughing)
（布兰妮和观众大笑）
Okay.
好的。
(All laughing)
（大家都笑了）
- You tripping.
- 你绊倒了。
I love kid, bah!
我爱孩子，呸！
You don't have no good story.
你没有好故事。
(audience laughing)
（观众笑）
(Britney laughs)
（布兰妮笑）
You tripping.
你绊倒了。
- I think it just was a breath of fresh air for people
- 我认为这对人们来说只是呼吸新鲜空气
to see something sweet and so innocent.
看到一些甜蜜而天真的东西。
- [Audience] Yes.
- [观众] 是的。
- Yeah. (audience applauding)
- 是的。 （观众鼓掌）
- [Britney] Here we go. (laughs)
- [布兰妮] 开始吧。 （笑）
- Let me ask y'all something.
- 让我问你们一件事。
Have y'all had a talk with them about it?
你们都跟他们谈过这件事了吗？
You haven't explained
你还没解释
to 'em that's- - No.
对他们来说那是——不。
- No, but they act like they're brothers
- 不，但他们表现得就像兄弟一样
and they call themselves brothers.
他们称自己为兄弟。
So we just-
所以我们只是——
- Let it go? - Yeah.
- 放手吧？ - 是的。
- Yeah, we're not gonna point out the differences.
- 是的，我们不会指出差异。
That defeats the purpose of
这违背了目的
what we- - 'Cause they don't see none.
我们--因为他们什么也看不见。
- That's right. - Yeah.
- 这是正确的。 - 是的。
- Because you know something? (audience applauding)
- 因为你知道一些事情？ （观众鼓掌）
You know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Because kids don't see difference.
因为孩子们看不出差异。
- Yeah. - They're taught differences.
- 是的。 - 他们被教导差异。
- [Viewer] Yes, sir.
- [观众] 是的，先生。
- If you go to any playground,
- 如果你去任何游乐场，
you see all the kids playing together.
你看到所有的孩子都在一起玩耍。
You don't see until they get older, them separating.
直到他们变老、分开时你才会看到。
That group over here eating.
那群人在这里吃饭。
That other group over there eating.
那边的另一组人正在吃饭。
You don't see that
你没有看到这一点
'cause they get taught to them.
因为他们是被教导的。
(Steve smacks lips)
（史蒂夫咂嘴）
That's what, if we could learn from kids, man.
如果我们能向孩子们学习的话，那就是这样。
Man, this world would be
伙计，这个世界将会是
a sure cooler place. - Yes.
一个绝对凉爽的地方。 - 是的。
(audience applauding)
（观众鼓掌）
- Man, it really, really would man.
- 伙计，真的，真的会伙计。
Well, hey, fellas.
好吧，嘿，伙计们。
I wanna thank you
我想谢谢你
for all of us how to live.
对于我们所有人如何生活。
(audience applauding) (Britney mutters)
（观众鼓掌）（布兰妮嘀咕）
- [Audience] Yeah.
- [观众] 是的。
I think that you two are the best friends.
我认为你们两个是最好的朋友。
I think you look just alike.
我觉得你们长得很像。
- [Britney] Yes.
- [布兰妮] 是的。
- I love the fact that you're twins.
- 我喜欢你们是双胞胎这一事实。
(audience cheering) And have a good life.
（观众欢呼）祝你生活愉快。
And y'all should stay friends forever.
你们应该永远保持朋友关系。
(audience cheering and applauding)
（观众欢呼鼓掌）
And thank y'all for coming.
感谢大家的到来。
Thank y'all.
谢谢大家。
(audience applauding)
（观众鼓掌）
Thank you very much.
非常感谢。
Hey, you made it to the end of this video.
嘿，您已经看到了本视频的结尾。
I got a lot more that you're gonna enjoy.
我还有很多你会喜欢的。
So just click to watch the next one
所以只需点击观看下一篇
and make sure you subscribe
并确保您订阅
to always know what's happening.
始终知道发生了什么。